A control plane for coding agents.
Run, supervise, and review — from any device.
Built for headless agent execution.
Agents run in the dark.
No visibility into reasoning or tool calls.
No approval gates for risky operations.
No way to intervene mid-run.
See every job at a glance.
Kanban board tracks queued, running, and review states.
Multiple agents run in parallel.
Each job runs in its own git worktree.
Write a prompt. Pick your agent and model.
Choose a permission mode.
Full auto, review & approve, or observe only.
One click to launch.
Watch the agent think in real time.
Reasoning, tool calls, and plan progress stream live.
Approval gates pause on risky actions.
Approve, reject, or trust the session.
Send operator messages to steer the agent.
Review every change before it lands.
Syntax-highlighted side-by-side diffs.
Browse the full workspace, not just changed files.
Merge, create a PR, or discard.
Track token usage and costs across the fleet.
Compare models by cost and performance.
No more invisible token burn.
Headless. Remote-first. Open.
CodePlane — control your coding agents.